日本語字幕仕上げ：光川  光荣字幕组（www.koeigame.cn）
オ～　オ～　オ～　俺たちの誇り
オ～　オ～　オ～  赤と黒のイレブン
オ～　オ～　オ～  イースト　トーキョー　ユナイテッド
Alright, let's keep our voices up for the match!
よ～し　よし
しっかり声出していくぞ！
集中しろよ！
Focus! If you let your guard down, they'll send us to the cleaners!
集中切らした 一気に　やられちまうぞ
Side-backs, stick close to Katayama and Hatake.
片山と畑には　しつこく  ついていけよ
サイド２人！
Yes!
オス！
Alright, I'm calm.
よし 落ち着いてるぞ　俺
I'll show you! I'll show you! I'll show you!
やってやる…  やってやる…　やってやる…
Sera's fired up, but he looks kinda scary.
気合い入ってんな  世良さん
ちょっと　怖いけど
Listen up, we did everything we could.
よ～し　いいか！
俺たちは　やる事はやった
Now we just have to show it on the pitch!
あとは　それ ピッチで出すだけだ
We'll defeat Osaka. Let's go!
大阪倒すぞ！
行くぞ！
Yeah!
Just you watch.
見てろってんだ
この９０分で
I'm going to snap your stuck-up nose in the next 90 minutes, Dulfer.
そのデカッ鼻  へし折ってやるよ　ダルファー
United we stand,Fly a flag 風を受け止めて
United we stand, Fly a flag!
kaze o uketomete
風を受け止めて
Let the wind blow through you
United we stand,Fly a flag たなびけ勝利のflag
United we stand, Fly a flag!
tanabike shouri no flag
たなびけ勝利の flag
Let the victory flag trail in the wind
遥かなゴールを信じて 走り続けていて
haruka na gooru o shinjite
遥かなゴールを信じて
Believe in the goal that lies in wait and keep running
hashiri tsuzuketeke
走り続けてけ
日々夢紡ぐ者達へ 降り注げ光よ
hibi yume tsumugu monotachi e furisosoge hikari yo
日々夢紡ぐ者達へ降り注げ光よ
Let light pour down upon the weaver of dreams
汗は裏切らないって 唇噛み締め
ase wa uragiranaitte kuchibiru kamishime
汗は裏切らないって唇噛み締め
Your sweat won't betray you, so bite down on your lips
何度も立ち上がり 大地を駆け抜ける
nandomo tachiagari daichi o kakenukeru
何度も立ち上がり大地を駆け抜ける
And stand back up again and again as you dash across the earth
yume ni owari wa naitte me o kagayakase
夢に終わりはないって 目を輝かせ
Our dreams never end, so keep on shining
Let's start now GIANT KILLING!
For the right! Hold on tight!
for the right
hold on tight
My story...
my story…
forever
Forever...
So, they're using man-to-man marking?
イースト　トーキョー　ユナイテッド
意気込みは買うがね　タツ
I commend your spirit, Tatsumi...
but do you really think this will be enough to contain my players?
ウチの選手を　１対１で  抑え込めると思うのかね
Kubotan!
クボタン
窪田のマークが杉江！
Sugie is marking Kubota?
じゃあ　ハウアーには…
Then who's marking Hauer?
…んだよ
Problem?
What's this?
何なんだ　一体？
This isn't what Coach said.
コーチから聞いてた話と違うぞ
Shouldn't No.3 be the one marking me?
僕には　３番 マークにつくんじゃないのか
Why is it...
なのに　何で　こんな…
あぁ？　何見てんだよ
What are you looking at?
...this unrefined brat?
小さくて  ガラの悪そうなヤツが…
おいおい　ハウアーのマーク　クロで大丈夫  かよ！
Can Kuro really take on Hauer?
The difference in height is too great!
身長差ありすぎんだろ
Just shut up and watch!
うっせ～よ　お前ら！
黙って見てやがれ～！
Telling his fans to shut up...
サポーターに黙れって…
How could he hear us from there?
つ～か　なんて地獄耳だよ
It's only a 20cm difference.
たかだか２０センチの  違いじゃねえか
This actually gets me more fired up.
逆に燃えるぜ　こん畜生
Sugie on Kubota... Kuroda on Hauer...
クボタに　スギ
ハウアーに　クロダか
That's quite a audacious match-up, Tatsumi.
随分と大胆な  マッチアップだな　タツミ
Don't get put off by this, Shimura.
Show them how bad these match-ups are.
It's a weird match-up...
変な組み合わせ…
But...
だけど
let's see what happens when I cross the ball in.
とりあえ 入れてみよ
やっぱり当たり強い！
That's spot on!
よこせ　ハウアー
Hauer, pass it here!
片山来てるぞ 清川
Katayama's coming, Kiyokawa!
Got it!
オーライ
Stop me if you can!
ヘッ　止められるもんな 止めてみいや
I can't afford to lose out in a one-on-one duel!
サイドの選手が　１対１で  負けてたまるか！
Don't let him pass you, Kiyokawa!
抜かせんな 清川！
He's faster than I thought, but...
思ったより 速そうやな　こいつ
せやけど…
A feint and he's left biting dust...
すぐフェイントとか 引っ掛かりそうやわ
Hey, Kubota!
ヘイ　クボタ！
I won't let the ball reach Hauer!
ハウアーに入れさせるか！
あ…　え～っと
Uhh...
This way.
こっちだ
It went over!
ワク外れた～
That was close!
あっぶねえ！
Gunners…
Hey, Hatake!
おい　コラ　畑！
Why did you shoot, you fool? What were you thinking?
何でお前が打つんじゃ　ボケ
何考えとんねん
Why? Because I'm the ace striker after all.
そんなもん　俺がエースに  決まっとるからやろ！
Don't be such a loser!
負け惜しみ言うな　アホンダラ！
You, the ace?
誰がエースや
What, you want a fight?!
やんのかい　ボケ！
They're getting into our half already.
い…　いきなり　フィニッシュまで  行かれましたね
Will we be okay?
大丈夫でしょうか
That was dangerous indeed.
思いっ切り危なかったねぇ
M-Manager! Where's your confidence?
か　監督！　自信持って～
I-It's right here.
い　いや…　持ってるけどね
But I thought that we'd have the upper hand...
こっちのほう 休み１日　多かったから
since we had an extra day to rest.
余裕持って試合に入れるか 思ったけど
As I thought, teams on a winning streak do look different.
やっぱり勝ち続けてるチームは  違うねぇ
They're picking up where they left off during the last game.
前の試合の勢いを  そのまま維持してやがる
チッ　あのデカブツめ
This giant brat...
I'll get dominated if I play my usual game.
普通に  やってたら押し切られちまうな
I've got to assess the situation and plan ahead accordingly.
もっと状況を読んで
１歩目を早くしねえとな
おっと　ワリイ
Oops, sorry.
Hey, you.
You're bumping into me too often.
あぁ？　何言ってんだ？
What're you saying?
Don't you know?
As a pro, you're being closely watched.
I pay attention to how I present myself,
so can you stop messing up my hair?
If you're really a pro, you should do something about it...
Your head.
なっ　なんか　今　伝わったぞ
I... I got that.
That transcended the language barrier!
言葉の壁を超えたぞ　コラ～！
テメエこそ
You're one to talk!
You're a guy! Yet you have that disgusting hairstyle!
男のくせ 気持ち悪い頭しやがって！
似合ってねえんだ この青ヒゲ！
I kind of got that.
You mocked me, right?
What, you wanna fight?!
なんだ　コラ
やんのか　テメエ！
Are Kuroda and Hauer chatting, or fighting? They look busy.
なんか　黒田とハウアーが…
…会話？
ケンカ？…してるんですけど
ハッ　さすがだね　クロ
Kuro's not too shabby. He held up well on his own.
やられてねえな
I'm counting on you. The fate of the first half lies in your hands.
頼むぜ
序盤は お前の出来にかかってんだ
Alright, let's show them what we've got!
こっちも  見せ場　作ろうぜ　ＥＴＵ！
That's too much, it'll hit the sideline.
長い　これは タッチライン割るな
This guy's from the back!
あ！　こいつ　俊足の…
That's too bad.
あ～　惜しい！
It would've been a good chance.
追いついてりゃ チャンスだったのに！
椿 椿…
He has great feet... No.7, Tsubaki.
なんで足だよ　７番　椿
椿 椿…
I guess I have to watch out for this guy.
やっぱり　こいつは要注意だな
ハハッ　ごめんよ　バッキー
Sorry, Baki.
He miscued it? That's unlike him.
パスミスか？
だとしたら珍しい
He did miss the last game because of his foot injury though.
ジーノのやつ
前の試合　足に違和感が  あるとかで欠場してたけど
Could it be...
ひょっとしたら…
Hey, Shimura, pass me the ball!
なんだ　コラ～！
What?
This prick, I'm gonna trounce him!
Like I'll lose to you, you idiot!
テメエなんかに負けるか　ボケ
Hmm, did the two of you become friends?
へえ 友達になったのか
You can't be too friendly during the match.
けど　試合中は  あんまり仲よくしちゃいけないよ
Here it is!
Bring it on!
来い　コラ～！
Fight!
勝負
ポスト入った
He's in position. Don't lose your man!
マーク外されんなよ　お前ら！
Give me the ball!
俺に　よこせや　ハウアー
Hauer!
It's here!
来やがった！
They're attacking!
仕掛けてきた
Kuroda!
黒田！
Stay calm.
落ち着いていけよ
よく対応した　黒田～
Good work, Kuroda!
ヘッ！　見たか このヘンチクリン頭！
Did you see that, you shit head?
Loose ball!
セカンドボール！
Nice, Kubo!
でかした　クボ
You bastard.
こいつ…
Nice defending, Kiyokawa.
ナイスディフェンス 清川
Good anticipation, Kiyokawa. Well done.
いい判断だ 清川
褒めてやるよ
Hey, your precious hair's messed up. Are you scared or something?
おいおい　自慢のヘアが乱れてるぜ
俺様に恐れでもなしたか？
This guy's making fun of me again!
こいつ　また僕を挑発してるな
This guy's just like the manager mentioned... He's bad with his feet.
この野郎　 監督の言ってたとおりだ
足元 まるで　うまくねえ
He's got a wider reach and he's taller than me,
リーチと高さは 向こうに分があるが
but what's crucial in defense is timing and positioning.
ディフェンスに重要なのは  タイミングと　ポジショニング
If I don't screw that up, I'll win!
それさえミスんなきゃ  俺は勝てる
I'll show you what's really important for centre backs.
センターバックにタッパなんて  関係ねえとこ　証明してやるよ
Interesting...
At first glance, they seem soft and sweet...
but on the inside they're not too fluffy.
These donuts are quite tasty.
What? You were talking about the donuts?
I've been feeling it for awhile now... this strange attraction.
Are those donuts really that good?
I'm not talking about the donuts! I'm talking about this match!
I don't quite link up with this guy...
つ…　ついていけねえ
Geez! What I'm talking about...
...is him! That Osaka player!
なんとか序盤  しのげますかね
I think we've survived the first few minutes.
We can finally get into the game...
こうなれば　ウチの形も 徐々に作れて…
I wish that was the case,
そうありたいけどね…
but we haven't got everything in control.
まだ抑えるべきところが 抑えきれてない
We've got to do that first,
まず そこを何とかしねえと
otherwise we'll be playing right into their hands.
このままじゃ　ズルズル～ッで 向こうのペースに…
Crap, he's realized that, too.
んな事　向こうも  分かってやがるか
Alright, they should be warmed up by now.
ETU haven't been really able to fend off our attacks.
The ball's in our court.
It's time to pile on the pressure!
Show them our proud footballing spirit!
Show them the diamond that has been perfected into beauty!
おお～　ダルファーが 攻めろ攻めろ光線　出してる
Dulfer is sending out "Attack, Attack" signals.
Alright, all four of them share the same sentiments.
４人とも同じ気持ちだね
Shimura... Osaka's attacks always start from his precise passes.
志村…
大阪の攻撃は  こいつの正確なフィードからだ
If I can put him off here...
ここを　もたつかせれば…
Shimu!
シム！
Even a half-hearted one is enough...
別に雑でも大丈夫なんだよ
ハウちゃんの　キープ力 そのくらい　すごいんだ
because Hauer's ball control is excellent.
Damn!
Yeah!
よっしゃ～！
Beat him!
ぶちかましたれや～！
Hauer, here!
こっちや　ハウアー
Katayama is charging in! Don't lose him, Kiyokawa!
片山が中に来てる
離されんな　清川～！
It's not for Katayama, it's Hatake!
片山じゃない
後ろの畑だ！
Alright!
おっしゃ～！
I won't let you shoot!
打たせるかよ
That's too weak, clear it!
弱えよ！
クリア　クリア～
This is where it begins, Tatsumi.
The might of our football.
Osaka's got the ball again!
また大阪ボール
Kubota got it!
拾ったのは窪田だ
What's with this guy?
何だよ　こいつ
He runs with the ball in a strange, unpredictable way.
チョコマカと　よく分かんねえ動きを
Tsubaki, trap him!
椿！　挟みに行け～
えっと
このっ！
おわっ！  杉江が股を通された
He nutmegged Sugie!
にゃろっ
It's Katayama!
片山だ
Stop him!
止めろ！
Watch this! This is my first goal in today's hat-trick!
見とれよ
これが　本日  ハットトリック予定しとる俺の
１点目！
どわ～　あっぶねえ！
That was close!
まだ来る
It's not over yet.
The one with the deciding factor is me, Kata!
決めんのは俺じゃ　カタ
What the hell are you doing? I'm gonna kill you, Hatake!
何すんねん…
殺すぞ　畑！
Are you stupid? That's my line!
アホかい！
俺のセリフだ　ボケ
Clear it! Clear it! Get it out!
クリアしろ　クリア～
いったん切れ
Kubota...
漥田
だ～っ！　セカンドボール 拾われまくりじゃねえか
They keep getting the loose balls.
We've got to snatch it and calm things down.
１回切って落ち着こうぜ！
What the hell is going on?
どうなっとるんだ　一体！
We can't retain the ball at all!
全然ボールが奪えんぞ～！
何とかせんか　達海
Do something, Tatsumi!
Osaka's attack is indeed scary,
確かに　大阪の攻撃に 肝を冷やしますが
but we've still managed to survive waves of attacks by them.
大事なの　その猛攻を形は
どうであれ しのげているという事です
選手たちは集中してます
The players are focused.
The game will definitely turn in our favour.
これなら我々にも必ず流れが来る
It will be alright.
きっと大丈夫です
We've trained hard to prepare for this match.
この試合のために
練習も 相当やったんですから
That's it, Akasaki! Stick to him!
そうそう　赤崎 フォローしていけ
う～し！
Alright.
ETU's got a pretty focused defense.
However,
how long they can keep it up?
Exactly.
Defenders usually let their guard down once the ball is cleared.
If the opponent keeps receiving the ball, then they're bound to lose focus eventually.
It's only a matter of time.
Then we've got them cornered.
The essence of Osaka Gunners' offensive style...
is to dominate possession in the opponent's half.
Short centre backs like me simply can't afford to lose to someone like you!
俺みたいな　背のない  センターバックはな
テメエみたいのだけには 負けられねえんだよ！
お～し！  負けてねえぞ　クロちゃん！
Alright! You won't lose, Kuroda!
Damn, they're still coming?
クソッ！　まだ攻撃続くのかよ
Come on! Focus! Focus!
おっと　集中しろ　集中
If I let my guard down, it'll be over,
油断したら一気にやられる
but this guy's only trying to beat me with speed.
でも　こいつ
スピードでしか勝負してこない
I can handle this.
今日の俺は対応できてる
I only need to get the timing right when he attacks.
ヤツの仕掛けてくる タイミングさえ気を付けていれば…
You're quite fast.
お前　いい足持っとんなぁ
I can't win against you with speed.
俺　スピードやったら  勝たれへんわ
Which is why...
せやから…
He's shooting?
打ってきた！
清川　抜かれた
Kiyokawa got beaten!
しまった
Crap!
Fool! You fell for it!
ヘッ アホが　だまされおって
He's cutting in, Dori!
中　切り込んでくるぞ　ドリ！
Damn! Kiyokawa, you idiot!
クソッ！
清川のバカが
Kuro, don't leave your man!
マーク外すな　クロ！
Katayama's coming!
片山　来た～！  行かせんな！
Don't let him pass!
Bring it. I'll stop you!
来るなら来てみろ 止めてやらあ
Don't take the bait! Watch Hauer, Kuro!
つられんな　クロ ハウアー見てろ！
A dink!
あ…　上げた
Tch...
You've got find the way to believe
carry on and carry on
Carry on and carry on
Till you can see tomorrow
I'll say 「never look back」
I'll say “never look back”
追い風を待って
oikaze o matte
Wait for the tailwind
そうchanceをのがすなら
sou chance o nogasunara
そう chance を逃すなら
And if you missed the chance
自分が風になれ no fears no tears
jibun ga kaze ni nare
自分が風になれ
Become the wind yourself
no tears,Yes Let it go！
No fears! No tears! Yes! Let it go!
Get tough！(Stay gold！)
Get tough! Get tough!
Stay gold!
Get tough！(We'll go！)
We'll go!
限界追い越せ
genkai oikose yuke
限界追い越せ行け
Surpass your limits and go!
行け キツイほど
kitsui hodo heart in red
キツイほど　heart in red
The harder it is the redder your heart will be!
heart in red
Go on! Go on!
Go on！(Stay cool！）
Stay cool!
Go on！(We'll go！)
We'll go!
asu wa mienai dakara
あすは見えないだから
Because we can't see into the future
あすは見えない だから
It's time to go
It's time to go yamerarenai
It's time to go やめられない
So it's time to go. We can't quit!
やめられない
Get tough!
Get tough！Get tough！ Get tough！
Get tough！(Stay gold！)
Get tough! Get tough!
Stay gold!
Get tough！(We'll go！)
We'll go!
共に乗り越えて 行け
tomo ni norikoete yuke
共に乗り越えて行け
Let's get through it together
見えるか It's daybreak there
mieruka It's daybreak there
Can you see that it's daybreak there?
Go on! Go on!
Go on！(Stay cool！) Go on！(We'll go！)
Stay cool!
We'll go!
予測できないだから
yosoku dekinai dakara
The future is unpredictable
It's time to go
It's time to go tomerarenai
It's time to go 止められない
So it's time to go. We can't stop!
止められない
I'm different today.
You're dwelling on the ball for far too long!
Your showtime's over!
Making use of that immense talent in the forward position...
Not too bad, Dulfer.